

19/04/1999

CONTACT

- +84 (03)67 005 758
- tutinh.nt@gmail.com
- Chua Lang, Dong Da, Ha Noi

EDUCATION

2017 - 2022 LE QUY DON TECHNICAL **UNIVERSITY (HA NOI)**

- Software Engineering
- CPA: 2.9

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Quality Check

PASTIMES

• In my free time, I work on some e-commerce website projects, read books, exercise and go experience things

NGUYEN TU TINH

DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I'm a web developer with 1.5 years of experience in NodeJS technologies, with knowledge of Object-Oriented Analysis and Design, and Database Design. Persistent in self-studying and learning new technologies, self-motivated, hardworking, responsible, and reliable, working effectively both independently and as a part of the team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AKB Software

Full Stack Developer

08/2022 - PRESENT

- I do outsourcing projects from Japan with different technologies.
- I participate in upgrading and maintaining a number of functional modules for a few domestic projects such as NS2HN management system, ADVSCM conference equipment control system.
- In addition, I am also a key developer for the ChungVui product project to create online invitations for user events, with the task of capturing the work of other team members and ensuring project quality

Antbot Vietnam Company

2021 - 2022

Junior Developer

- Participate in the project of Building a Military Science management support system of the General Department of Technology
- In addition, during this time I completed the graduation project on a dictionary lookup website combined with OCR using the FARM Stack.

TECHNICAL SKILL

- Programming Language: JavaScript, Java, HTML5, CSS3
- Frameworks/Flatforms: ReactJS, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, Web API, GraphQL
- Database Management Systems: PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Version Control: SVN, Git
- Foreign Language: English (Basics- 500 Toeic)
- Others: CI/CD of GitLab. Scrum development process